<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-03-31T01:31:56+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">News</title><subtitle>The Portal to the New, Open Internet.</subtitle><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network receives Arbitrum DAO airdrop</title><link href="/2023/03/23/mask-network-receives-arbitrum-dao-airdrop" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network receives Arbitrum DAO airdrop" /><published>2023-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2023/03/23/mask-network-receives-arbitrum-dao-airdrop</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/03/23/mask-network-receives-arbitrum-dao-airdrop">&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is thrilled and honored to receive 257,540 $ARB allocated by Arbitrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/arbitrum-dao-airdrop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ARB&amp;amp;src=cashtag_click&quot;&gt;$ARB&lt;/a&gt; tokens are received with our multi-sig wallet on arb1: &lt;strong&gt;0x3131Cc8Dcb6b88B371E0F288a13DCbD49e630B9A.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Signers of this wallet are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;0x8C246Fc819A91F19E6B56dd9a7970752D5b889F6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;0x74cF2e69f46d43dD5D14b1dbd03858d4698F7e7d&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;0xc5342CD71f67DAc44Bcfbc37df35700b5e4691e6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a long-term buidler of the Arbitrum community, Mask Network supported Arbitrum as part of the multi-chain wallet since 2022, users could display assets using the Mask Network extension. Mask Network would like to congratulate Arbitrum on its token launch and explore more possibilities about the decentralized social with Arbitrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The $ARB tokens allocated to the Mask Network DAO will be used to support our community and the buidl of amazing dapps. We will post another announcement in regards to the details of how the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ARB&amp;amp;src=cashtag_click&quot;&gt;$ARB&lt;/a&gt; tokens will be allocated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Mask Network is thrilled and honored to receive 257,540 $ARB allocated by Arbitrum.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">DWF Labs announces strategic $5M investment in Mask Network</title><link href="/2023/01/19/dwf-labs-announces-strategic-5m-investment-in-mask-network" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DWF Labs announces strategic $5M investment in Mask Network" /><published>2023-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2023/01/19/dwf-labs-announces-strategic-5m-investment-in-mask-network</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/01/19/dwf-labs-announces-strategic-5m-investment-in-mask-network">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/dwfxmask.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DWF Labs, the global digital asset management firm in the Web3 industry, is announcing a strategic investment and partnership in Mask Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DWF Labs has invested by purchasing $5M worth of $MASK tokens. The investment will be used to support the continuous building of a decentralized social network and the Mask Network ecosystem at large, to make Web3 more accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A pioneer in the decentralized social network space, Mask Network has been one of the earliest community members of the Bluesky protocol, the decentralized social network founded by Jack Dorsey, co-founder of Twitter. The Mask Network team has also been actively supporting some of the top instances of Mastodon, one of the largest decentralized social networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DWF Labs also made a $10M investment in the TON (The Open Network) ecosystem last November. TON Network is a third-generation proof-of-stake blockchain, initially designed in 2018 by the Durov brothers, the founders of Telegram Messenger. TON was designed to be fast, affordable, user-friendly, and fully scalable. Mask Network is also working with TON. In the future, social protocols and applications from the Mask Network ecosystem will integrate with TON and its relevant components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a multi-stage Web3 investment firm, DWF Labs has included multiple outstanding Web3 projects in its portfolio and with Mask Network onboard, DWF Labs is committed to supporting Mask Network’s aim to build a free, open internet that welcomes developers and users to enter the Web3 world. Mask Network has previously received support from private and institutional backers such as Arweave, Hard Yaka, Protocol Labs, and more. This partnership with DWF Labs will bring greater support for Mask Network and marks another milestone in their web3 journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-dwf-labs&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About DWF Labs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DWF Labs is the global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm present in Singapore, Switzerland, South Korea, the BVI, and the UAE and trades almost 2,000 pairs with a daily volume that places DWF Labs among the top 5 ranking entities trading on the world’s top 40 exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network Acquires Pawoo.net, one of the largest Mastodon instances</title><link href="/2022/12/21/mask-network-acquires-pawoo.net-one-of-the-largest-mastodon-instances" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network Acquires Pawoo.net, one of the largest Mastodon instances" /><published>2022-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/12/21/mask-network-acquires-pawoo.net-one-of-the-largest-mastodon-instances</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/12/21/mask-network-acquires-pawoo.net-one-of-the-largest-mastodon-instances">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/pawoo.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://mastodon.cloud/@TheAdmin/109563760376240629&quot;&gt;Social Co.&lt;/a&gt;, the entity affiliated with Mask Network has acquired Pawoo.net, one of the largest Mastodon instances. The new team will be taking over the operation and maintenance of Pawoo.net starting from December 21st, 2022, with no impact on existing users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pawoo, operated from Japan since 2017, is the second largest instance of Mastodon. It has drawn users from all over the world including illustrators, anime fans, novelists, and music enthusiasts since its inception. Accumulating around 800K users, Pawoo has become a “place to enjoy creative activity and unfettered communication.” The Pawoo acquisition marks another milestone of the Mask team towards the building of a decentralized social network and a free, open internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anticipation is riding high for decentralized social networks to emerge. As an open-source-based and decentralized social network, Mastodon, currently with 1.9 million monthly active users, has become the to-go choice for many users who believe in self-control and autonomy. Despite its functions like Twitter, Mastodon allows individual users to set up their own social networks and determine how it operates and what their users can share. Mask team has been the maintainer of two of the most active instances of Mastodon, mstdn.jp, and mastodon.cloud, and built the first official app for Mastodon collaborated with Mastodon core builder team and NYC-based design firm Lickability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2017 by a group of young believers in truly free and open internet, the Mask team aims to build an easy-to-use bridge from Web 2.0 to Web 3.0-era decentralized apps. As early as the end of 2019 Mask extension can support its users with secure, decentralized social messaging, payment networks, file storage and sharing upon the current mainstream social media networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Embracing the ownership economy and helping to build the next phase of decentralized social networks, Mask has obtained tens of thousands of users and has raised over US$50 million from private and institutional backers. To further its vision of building the decentralized social network ecosystem, Mask announced the launch of a US$42 million Bonfire Union fund in July 2022 to strategically invest in decentralized social networks, infrastructure, and creative content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a major Mastodon instance, Pawoo will have plenty of space to grow. The new operation team hopes to play a crucial role in driving its future growth. The team believes that on the journey to the free and open Internet, the decentralized infrastructure and applications are under development at a rapid pace. The future decentralized social networks including Pawoo will play an important role during this process to achieve a new and open internet.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Announcing the Mask Grant and Ecosystem Programs</title><link href="/2022/08/31/announcing-the-mask-grant-and-ecosystem-programs" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing the Mask Grant and Ecosystem Programs" /><published>2022-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-08-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/08/31/announcing-the-mask-grant-and-ecosystem-programs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/08/31/announcing-the-mask-grant-and-ecosystem-programs">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/grants-program-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past year, Mask Network has initiated a few programs including but not limited to the ETHShanghai Hackathon, scholarships, Gitcoin Grants Round 15 social ecosystem round, and onwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slowly but surely, we have outgrown our original products, including the Mask browser extension and Next.ID, and are forming a vaster ecosystem. As such, it’s time to officially announce Mask Network’s ecosystem programs for the public to participate in and get involved in a more structured and transparent way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We welcome open applications from projects of all areas to our ecosystem programs (4+). Besides the past programs, this is also the debut we made for the Mask grant program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-mask-network-ecosystem&quot;&gt;The Mask Network Ecosystem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has been consistently building the Web3 Social ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internally, we’ve been building Mask Network and Next.ID. Externally, we support Web3 projects via grants, investments, and hackathons. By doing these, we have grown an ecosystem of over 100 projects with wide coverage over social protocols, social apps, infrastructures, games, and social intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we couldn’t have achieved all these without our partners’ support. To name a few:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Our underlying layers include data providers such as DeBank, CoinGecko, NFTScan, Inspect, Biteye and Adot&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Our storage providers include Kwil, Arweave, Ceramic and IPFS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Other partners include our bandwidth provider Meson and security provider Runtime Verification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the support of these partners, Mask Network builds on them to deliver a set of Web3 native social products and DID protocols that offer users secure, rich, and decentralized experiences and make up for a thriving Web3 social ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mask.notion.site/Mask-Ecosystem-Overview-public-page-8170b5ed7e7f4424b45c060377108396ic-page-8170b5ed7e7f4424b45c060377108396&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Click to view Mask ecosystem public notion page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://miro.medium.com/max/1400/1*shk8jVU32EHV8F2aJDMZhA.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-to-expect-from-mask-network-ecosystem-programs&quot;&gt;What to expect from Mask Network ecosystem programs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network offers financial support and resources to Web3 startups of all stages, fields, and scales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seed-stage projects: Mask can be your one-stop incubator.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Non-profit projects: Mask can be your grant donor&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Growth-stage projects looking to scale: Bonfire Ecosystem Fund is your long-term partner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/ecosystem.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our Ecosystem Program by Stage&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;stages-of-our-ecosystem-programs&quot;&gt;Stages of our ecosystem programs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-hackathon&quot;&gt;1. Hackathon:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This summer, Mask successfully hosted ETH Shanghai hackathon. We invited intellectuals and developers to exchange their opinions on global Web3 collaborations, Ethereum 2.0, the decentralized Internet, NFT art, and philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are committed to promoting and encouraging more developers to join the global Web3 community through sponsoring more hackathons. We have sponsored the Moonshot hackathon with more to come in 2022. This year, we will double the sponsorship number to 5–10 hackathon organizers and continue to sponsor more hackathon programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View past winners &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ethshanghai.org/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;2-web3-scholarship--fellowship&quot;&gt;2. Web3 Scholarship &amp;amp; Fellowship:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web3 scholarship is an annual scholarship program designed for undergrad students, encouraging them to join Web3. In 2021, Mask has received applications from brilliant young minds and picked its qualified winners and we seek more web3 undergrad/dropout warriors. Last year, Mask picked 3 winners of the 100k scholarship. View more info &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/suji_yan/status/1464929882257772545&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;3-mask-bounty-program&quot;&gt;3. Mask Bounty program:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mask Bounty program contains a wide range of Web3 dApps or features, and you can integrate almost any dApp, whether DeFi, NFT, prediction market, Web3 social, or decentralized storage. You can always pick the bounties and start to buidl. Apply &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/dimensiondev/bounties&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;4-mask-grant-program-debuting-today&quot;&gt;4. Mask Grant Program (Debuting Today):&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mask Grant Program is a newly launched program that supports projects through funding by enriching their value in Web3 and Mask’s Ecosystem. With a history of product-building, a solid reputation, and broad connections, MaskDAO wants to share its resources and facilitate collaboration to accelerate the ecosystem’s growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Grant Program offers applicants two options which are the public goods track and the ecosystem track. The public goods track is perfect for projects that aim to create long-term value for the Web3 ecosystem. The ecosystem track is tailored for projects that contribute to the Mask ecosystem with a positive value-add impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The application process:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step 1: Submit your &lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/WxCfhdAyBne6V46D7&quot;&gt;application form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step 2: Application review time &amp;amp; selected interviews&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step 3: Application result notification&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step 4: Onboarding + Milestone Setting + Mentor matching&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step 5: Launch and Exit Interview&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to fund around 50 projects for the first year with an average check of $MASK worth of 10k USD ($MASK worth of 500k USD, with 10+ candidates already).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The grant program is now open for &lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/WxCfhdAyBne6V46D7&quot;&gt;public applications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://mask.notion.site/Mask-Grant-Program-4b177b18925f4c57b2346d6ec85e641d&quot;&gt;Mask Grant Program notion&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;5-gitcoin-round&quot;&gt;5. Gitcoin round:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has been an active supporter of Gitcoin since GR6 and has posted over 50 bounties. For GR14, Mask is the sole sponsor of Web3 Social Ecosystem Round. The matching pool was $50k in total. Mask believes this is a fantastic way to let our community decide which projects deserve funding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask will keep sponsoring more Gitcoin rounds for the following GR15 and so on. View past events &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/blog/gr14-announce/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;6-investment-fund&quot;&gt;6. Investment fund:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our investment fund consists of two parts, the Bonfire Union ecosystem fund, and the Mask token swap fund. Bonfire ecosystem fund started investments on Q2 2021 and recently announced the first closing of $42 million. We have seen stellar growth from a bunch of our portfolio projects including RSS3, Meson Network, and rct.ai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the Mask token swap fund focuses on strategic alignment with some of our partner projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the Bonfire Union &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2022/07/06/bonfire-union-mask-network-maiden-fund/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the token swap fund &lt;a href=&quot;https://snapshot.org/#/masknetwork.eth/proposal/QmTNXDrx2xwrFZoU96dfPXe8p5DwCmZLBEGc7VoxMU66eL&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network’s ecosystem is looking to expand and include more innovative projects. Check out this table to pick which program fits you best!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://miro.medium.com/max/1400/0*XzpUfKqS5ZQHL2Hp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/WxCfhdAyBne6V46D7&quot;&gt;Mask Grant Application Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/grants/new&quot;&gt;Gitcoin Grant Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/suji_yan/status/1464929882257772545&quot;&gt;Details about past scholarship event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/dimensiondev/bounties&quot;&gt;Bounty application link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Investment fund email: bonfire@mask.io&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;snapshot-proposal-regarding-budgetary-requests-for-ecosystem-programs&quot;&gt;Snapshot proposal regarding budgetary requests for ecosystem programs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has completed our Web3 ecosystem vision partially, and we need voters’ help to have a bigger impact on builders. We need more funds to systematically push programs forward as well as better support the early-stage web3 projects. Our aim is to fund about 50 Grant projects in Web3 and public utilities annually and grow users of the ecosystem products to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask DAO has submitted a snapshot proposal which will require $MASK equivalent to 1 million USD for Mask Ecosystem Programs, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mask Grant program (500k USD worth of $MASK in total, with 10+ candidates)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gitcoin Grant (200k USD worth of $MASK, already allocated 50k)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scholarship &amp;amp; Hackathon (250k USD worth of $MASK)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bounties (50k USD worth of $MASK, already funded over 30 projects)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-vote-for-the-proposal&quot;&gt;How to vote for the proposal?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://snapshot.org/#/masknetwork.eth&quot; title=&quot;https://snapshot.org/#/masknetwork.eth&quot;&gt;https://snapshot.org/#/masknetwork.eth&lt;/a&gt; and find this proposal and click the button to vote.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Blooming together with Lens Protocol, Mask Network invites its community member to join a decentralized, non-custodial social graph</title><link href="/2022/08/16/blooming-together-with-lens-protocol-mask-network-invites-its-community-member-to-join-a-decentralized-non-custodial-social-graph" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blooming together with Lens Protocol, Mask Network invites its community member to join a decentralized, non-custodial social graph" /><published>2022-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/08/16/blooming-together-with-lens-protocol-mask-network-invites-its-community-member-to-join-a-decentralized-non-custodial-social-graph</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/08/16/blooming-together-with-lens-protocol-mask-network-invites-its-community-member-to-join-a-decentralized-non-custodial-social-graph">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/lens-01.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is thrilled to announce a collaboration with Lens Protocol, a composable and decentralized social graph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The need and prospect for web3 social networks are growing. This trend toward a more open, transparent social graph — where digital data, audience, and content assets could be owned by users — benefits creators, developers, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network and Lens Protocol have a shared vision, and we are ready to show such a vision on the product level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future, we look to collaborate closely together and move forward with the product integration from both sides; by bringing and leveraging Lens’ composability and open-source code, Mask Network will enable users to follow, like, mirror Lens content on top of Mask’s major products such as the browser extension and our upcoming Web3 info-feed mobile app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking about more potential collaborations — — with the possible integration with Next.ID, the Decentralized-Identity-as-a-Service (DIaaS) provider of Mask Network, will make Web3 a native and smooth social experience combined with Web2, providing users with approaches to seamlessly cross-post on RSS3, Lens, Twitter, etc…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To kick off this collaboration, Lens Protocol will give out ~3,000 Lens handles to the Mask Network community. Active community members of Mask Network will be eligible to claim a profile handle. You can check if your wallet address is on the active member list &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qgSu3JHEYMINjrrIvBcKM1Gu3GtP_liJo7AwPlWL4xs/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The list includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Addresses that have interacted with finance dApps on Mask extension multiple times&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Holders of Mask’s past event POAP(s)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Holders of MaskOn PFP (our community-initiated NFT project) as of July 19th&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Addresses that are eligible to claim 5+ OATs in Mask past events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/lens-02.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eligible users may claim at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://claim.lens.xyz/&quot; title=&quot;https://claim.lens.xyz/&quot;&gt;https://claim.lens.xyz/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from existing active members, Mask Network has also been granted 500 Lens handles for other members of the Mask Network community. 500 lucky members who have verified their accounts with Mask Network will be able to get a claimable Lens handle. We will announce the winners list on our Twitter @realMaskNetwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To flourish this beautiful garden for the Mask community members and Lens bloomers, we wish to plant more seeds full of potential and excitement for the future-generation social network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-lens-protocol&quot;&gt;About Lens Protocol&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://lens.xyz/&quot;&gt;Lens Protocol&lt;/a&gt; is a decentralized, non-custodial social graph. Lens implements unique, on-chain social interaction mechanisms analogous to commonly understood Web2 social media interactions, but significantly expanded with unique functionality that empowers communities to form and participants to own their own social graph.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network Integrates Next.ID As Its Decentralized Identity Provider</title><link href="/2022/07/21/mask-network-integrates-next.id-as-its-decentralized-identity-provider" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network Integrates Next.ID As Its Decentralized Identity Provider" /><published>2022-07-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/07/21/mask-network-integrates-next.id-as-its-decentralized-identity-provider</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/21/mask-network-integrates-next.id-as-its-decentralized-identity-provider">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/img_2909.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is proud to announce that we’re partnering with &lt;a href=&quot;https://next.id/&quot;&gt;Next.ID&lt;/a&gt; as its Decentralized-Identity-as-a-Service (DIaaS) of choice. Mask Network’s major overarching goal is to be a bridge for all internet users to eventually gain exposure and understanding of Web3, and this is a huge step in that direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-nextid&quot;&gt;What is Next.ID?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next.ID is a decentralized identity aggregator that’s building the base layer of identities. It takes a unique approach to decentralized identities by seamlessly integrating both Web2 and Web3 accounts, creating a highly interoperable layer where both coexist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This allows, for example, Twitter users to create social networks with MetaMask holders, building completely new social networks from the ground up in a permissionless manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s empowered to do this via 3 technical innovations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ProofService, a blockchain-like model that ensures data integrity&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;KVService, data organization and storage to keep information flow seamless&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;RelationService, an aggregator that integrates existing IDs, ID queries, and IDs bound to and in parallel to Next.ID&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Next.ID/next-id-aggregates-identities-across-web2-and-web3-giving-data-ownership-back-to-users-97818034e956&quot;&gt;Next.ID and what it means for the Web3 Identity ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-nextid&quot;&gt;Why Next.ID?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is committed to working with decentralized protocols with the same vision: an interconnected space not dominated by any single entities. Next.ID’s founding principles as a DIaaS facilitates such a future, working with – instead of competing with – other DID providers to build an interoperable future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network Welcomes Terry Branstad &amp;amp; Steven Churchill with the Branstad Churchill Group, LLC. as Strategic Advisors</title><link href="/2022/07/11/mask-network-welcomes-terry-branstad-steven-churchill-with-the-branstad-churchill-group-llc.as-strategic-advisors" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network Welcomes Terry Branstad &amp; Steven Churchill with the Branstad Churchill Group, LLC. as Strategic Advisors" /><published>2022-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/07/11/mask-network-welcomes-terry-branstad-steven-churchill-with-the-branstad-churchill-group-llc.as-strategic-advisors</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/07/11/mask-network-welcomes-terry-branstad-steven-churchill-with-the-branstad-churchill-group-llc.as-strategic-advisors">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/0_vdnbzvvv9wcn14t3.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is pleased to announce that former U.S. Ambassador to China and Governor of Iowa, Terry Branstad, and his former Chief of Staff at the U.S. Embassy in Beijing, Steven Churchill have officially joined the non-profit arm of Mask Network as Strategic Advisors, effective immediately. In this new role, Branstad and Churchill will make history as the first former US policymakers to formally join the Web3 community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two men have taken on this new role because they believe small businesses are the backbone of the economy and to drive growth, they must be empowered. With Web3 capturing the attention of some of the brightest minds coming out of higher education in the United States and abroad, Branstad and Churchill feel it is important to empower the Web3 community and importantly, to provide guardrails to reduce and discourage malicious activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A historic moment for Web3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This announcement is a milestone event for Web3. Ambassador Branstad (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ambassador-terry-branstad-181ba6210/&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;) and Mr. Churchill (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/steve-churchill-7258535/&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;) are the first former elected officials and diplomats to serve in the capacity as advisors for a Web3 project, paving the way for greater transparency and governmental and regulatory engagement. As advisors, the two men will provide strategic advice to the Mask Network team to help inform future launch strategies, and provide clarity related to the governance structure to help grow the global impact of Mask Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ambassador Branstad was a featured speaker at the ETH Shanghai Summit in May 2022, and met with Suji Yan, Mask Network founder last month. Ambassador Branstad was impressed with Suji’s vision to build the foundation for a more open, transparent, and decentralized network using Web3 technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Strategic Advisors for Mask Network, Branstad and Churchill will share their wealth of experience concerning international relations and cross-border commerce in the non-profit arm of Mask Network, to help Mask to navigate regulatory environments in multiple markets, enabling talented builders within Mask Network’s ecosystem to go global.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Terry Branstad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terry Branstad is the former U.S. Ambassador to China (2017–2020), and Governor of Iowa (1983–1999/2011–2017). He holds the distinction as the longest serving governor in the history of the United States. Branstad has decades of experience in state and local government and international affairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Steven Churchill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steven Churchill served as the Chief of Staff at the U.S. Embassy in Beijing, working with Terry Branstad to advance strategic priorities for the Embassy in China. He was elected to the Iowa Statehouse at the age of 29 and has a wealth of experience in federal, state, and local government. He has extensive knowledge as an executive in the nonprofit arena and holds a master’s degree in Nonprofit Administration (MNA).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">How to unfuck Web2? And why decentralized social networks are inevitable.</title><link href="/2022/04/26/how-to-unfuck-web2-and-why-decentralized-social-networks-are-inevitable" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to unfuck Web2? And why decentralized social networks are inevitable." /><published>2022-04-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/04/26/how-to-unfuck-web2-and-why-decentralized-social-networks-are-inevitable</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/26/how-to-unfuck-web2-and-why-decentralized-social-networks-are-inevitable">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://vip2.loli.io/2022/04/26/OiNWlnze3ZJfT6a.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Once we have surrendered our senses and nervous systems to the private manipulation of those who would try to benefit from taking a lease on our eyes and ears and nerves, we don’t really have any rights left. Leasing our eyes and ears and nerves to commercial interests is like handing over the common speech to a private corporation, or like giving the earth’s atmosphere to a company as a monopoly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— —&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Understanding-Media-Extensions-Marshall-McLuhan/dp/0262631598&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Understanding Media: The Extensions of Man&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;by Herbert Marshall McLuhan, 1964&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-time-has-come-for-decentralized-social-networks&quot;&gt;The time has come for decentralized social networks.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Building upon the reconstructions of the monetary system, financial market, and labor forces in the scheme of the Web3 revolution, we are now at a historical turning point where the decentralization of social networks is inevitable. Cyber citizens need a new-age public forum and information market that align with the values of decentralized cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social networks have practically served as a digital public discourse infrastructure for decades, and their role as public infrastructure (Social Network as a Utility) will grow to be pertinent in Web3, creating tensions with the current centralized profit-driven platform model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evidence has shown that centralized social media platforms in Web2 are stifling innovations of third parties and hitting the glass ceiling in their own growth. Decentralization is the most optimal way out for new builders and giants themselves. Witnessing how Web3 technologies (blockchain, cryptography, P2P networks) have shaken the order in the global economy gives us enough faith for the rise of a new order in the digital public discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding and being part of the historic movement towards decentralized social networks will make it easier for us — builders, investors, and cyber citizens — to remain agile and relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;social-networks-at-their-core-provide-digital-public-infrastructure-for-information-exchanges-and-human-interactions&quot;&gt;Social networks at their core provide digital public infrastructure for information exchanges and human interactions.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://vip2.loli.io/2022/04/26/TYtnuwkSrEvmeyP.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each generation of the web sparked innovations and native ways for cyber citizens to share information, but also comes with its own deficiencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web1 was about open protocols that were decentralized and community-governed. Most of the value accrued to the edges of the network — &lt;a href=&quot;https://future.a16z.com/why-web3-matters/&quot;&gt;users and builders&lt;/a&gt;. Cyber citizens, granted you know how to host servers and build websites, were free to share information publicly. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/cyberspace-independence&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Declaration of the Independence of Cyberspace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the Internet is a place to flourish idealism and radical individualism without national borders. However, Web1 didn’t provide an ideal marketplace where “online social relationship” was reflected and enhanced. Thus, Web1’s network was shaped to be more of a few-to-many public broadcast. The distribution channels of content were also more decentralized, making it more difficult for large-scale public debates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emergence of social networks as we know them today, the so-called Web2 giants like Twitter and Facebook, solves the lack of an idea marketplace in the previous era. Through a centralized platform, the social relations and dialogues in the physical world started to morph into the online world. While social media platforms serve as public forums for civil discourse and scrutiny of the government–similar to the Ekklesia of Athens in the cyber era, the platforms are owned by private corporations. Big corporations led by the likes of &lt;a href=&quot;https://web3revolution.typlog.io/episodes/danny&quot;&gt;Mark Zuckerberg built castles&lt;/a&gt; in the name of privacy protection. Users were trapped in feudal cities and adopted the “user” mindset, which weakened people’s agency endowed by the Internet. When “netizens” become “users,” we gradually become Zuckerberg’s data. From public facilities to closed castles, the social network form of Web2 is becoming more and more alienated and distorted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Web2 social network is similar to any other &lt;em&gt;intermediate form&lt;/em&gt; brought about by past technological revolutions, where private corporations functioned as the providers of public facilities. To make profits from this model, these privatized social networks have two ways to earn: 1. collect rents from advertisers and 2. exploit regulatory arbitrage and side with certain political tailwinds, algorithmically censoring and distorting information flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is the ultimate dilemma&lt;/strong&gt;: as social networks start to be tempted by commercial interests and political pressure, they become less effective as public service providers. But if they go against their corporatist interests, the capital market would punish them with plummeting stock prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;when-web2s-social-networks-fail-as-public-forums-so-whats-the-path-forward&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;When Web2’s social networks fail as public forums, so what’s the path forward?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both in the Web2 tech ecosystems of China and the US, people attempted to carry out reforms from within but have rarely succeeded. We have seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vice.com/en/article/a3mm4z/the-rise-and-demise-of-rss&quot;&gt;decline of the RSS feed&lt;/a&gt; and how Facebook suppressed Friendly Social Browser in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2020/11/once-again-facebook-using-privacy-sword-kill-independent-innovation%23:\~:text%3DFriendly%2520is%2520a%2520web%2520browser%252C%2520so%2520it%2520is%2520our%2520understanding,%25E2%2580%259D%2520Facebook%253B%2520Facebook%2520users%2520do.&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;source=docs&amp;amp;ust=1650898398807095&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2iZrW8isqzGfXUGv0CwHPb&quot;&gt;the name of privacy&lt;/a&gt; while inappropriately handling its data with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/mar/17/cambridge-analytica-facebook-influence-us-election&quot;&gt;Cambridge Analytica&lt;/a&gt;. In China, developers of third-party extensions on top of Tencent’s QQ even faced jail time. These are just the tip of an iceberg of the stifled innovations of third-party developers on centralized platforms. Fundamentally, Web2 social networks cannot reconcile their needs to profit and reduce regulatory risks with the values and social impact created by new applications built over the top that are outside of their commercial jurisdiction. They chose survival as a competitive business entity over what could be beneficial for the broader ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As developers and general netizens wake up to reclaim their cyber citizenship, sponsored by a maturing decentralized crypto-native economy and an increasingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/you-yes-you-would-be-a-better-owner-for-twitter-than-elon-musk/&quot;&gt;broad ideological consensus&lt;/a&gt; to challenge the centralized social network — it’s time for disruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We see &lt;strong&gt;two paths&lt;/strong&gt; forward in light of Web2 platforms’ failure to serve as public forum providers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://vip2.loli.io/2022/04/26/PbXQxwl9IosaSjN.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web3 native protocols and applications overtake incumbents.&lt;/strong&gt; Using cryptography and blockchain, we are witnessing the revival of the RSS feed with enhanced usability built on top of RSS3 and how users can communicate and transact cryptically on Twitter using over-the-top Web3 layers such as Mask Network. Insights on social graphs and social interactions are no longer monopolized by walled gardens, as we see increasing DApps built on top of open-sourced Lens Protocol, RSS3 and Cyber Connect. Our vision for Web 3 social networks will incorporate the protocol-first decentralized governance ethos of Web 1 with the enhanced usability and social elements we love about Web2.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The current social network giants will undo their past, rethink, and restructure the business models and relationships with their users.&lt;/strong&gt; We see Web2 networks like Twitter and Telegram to be the activists in this regard. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-twitter-set-accept-musks-best-final-offer-sources-2022-04-25/&quot;&gt;As Elon Musk seals $44 billion deal for Twitter and pledges to change Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, here is a wild thought experiment: imagine the future commercial value of Twitter to be not measured by its P&amp;amp;L as a private corporation but as the most robust social network ecosystem powered by Web3 protocols and allowing more protocols to access its open API. Telegram is beating the curve and already welcomed dozens of third-party applications growing over the top. In such a case, Twitter and Telegram would come close to being an open and impartial public forum infrastructure providers — the way social networks were intended to be. In fact, a big part of today’s Web3-related discussions and new decentralized applications actually take place on Twitter. Regardless of who will own Twitter in the next decade, we hope its owner(s) can recognize such a trend of Twitter and consider its potential as a decentralized social network and ecosystem provider.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-emergence-of-decentralized-social-networks-is-inevitable&quot;&gt;The emergence of decentralized social networks is inevitable.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the era of Web3, social networks still play the role of the marketplace of ideas and public forums. The Web3 revolution is cultural, financial, and social, and the impact of this revolution will permeate every corner of cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this perspective, the preconditions of the revolution are all in place:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An independent treasury (BTC, ETH)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A separate financial system (Defi)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Independent art and culture alliance (NFT)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New ways of human collaboration and organizing labor forces (DAOs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://vip1.loli.io/2022/04/26/pDr89bgSsNOKvHY.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The missing jigsaw piece is a new infrastructure and ecosystem for cyber citizens to gather and participate in public discourse. Today, most people are largely using the Web2 communication tech stack (Discord, Twitter, Telegram, Google) to do so, but the various restrictions of Web2 social networks will inevitably make the early Web3 adopters feel restricted and call for changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, we don’t want to renounce the value and importance of Web2 social media. The platform effect of Web2 social networks can amplify voices and mobilize massive actions. Web3 revolution is spreading like wildfire thanks to such effect. Digital citizens have also become accustomed to using social networks to share and receive information daily, establishing social media as an infrastructure for the functioning of a cyber society. The goal of the Web3 social networks is not to build a blockchain replica of the Web2 giants, but to use innovative designs and technologies to counter the centralized and monopolistic behavior of Web2, to wrestle back the right to information and digital identities from the platforms to the netizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From new financial systems to new cultural symbols, then to the organization of labor forces, the Web3 revolution is here. These preconditions build up the pursuit of an open, transparent, and impartial public forum and information marketplace, free of political interference, for the Web3 citizens who long for freedom and autonomy. Now, the latest stage of this revolution is decentralized social networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“It is much harder for participants in decentralized systems to collude to act in ways that benefit them at the expense of other participants”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;― Vitalik Buterin, 2017&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I would choose freedom over comfort every time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;― George R.R. Martin&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authors&lt;/strong&gt;: Suji Yan (&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/suji_yan&quot;&gt;@suji_yan&lt;/a&gt;); Hehe Shen (&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/hannah_h2s&quot;&gt;@hannah_h2s&lt;/a&gt;); Hana-chan (&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/hanachanweb3&quot;&gt;@hanachanweb3&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network receives strategic investment from Hard Yaka</title><link href="/2022/04/14/mask-network-receives-strategic-investment-from-hard-yaka" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network receives strategic investment from Hard Yaka" /><published>2022-04-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/04/14/mask-network-receives-strategic-investment-from-hard-yaka</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/04/14/mask-network-receives-strategic-investment-from-hard-yaka">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/hard-yaka.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has received a strategic investment from Hard Yaka to build foundations in strategic development in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard Yaka is founded by Greg Kidd. Kidd was not only the first-round investor and prior advisor of Twitter, Square(Block) but also worked closely with Jack Dorsey, who recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/twitter-funded-social-media-project-bluesky-adds-jack-dorsey-board-2022-02-08/&quot;&gt;joined the bluesky board&lt;/a&gt;, of which Mask Network is a founding community member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/wx20220418-165610-2x.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bluesky-community.net/&quot; title=&quot;https://bluesky-community.net/&quot;&gt;https://bluesky-community.net/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from Twitter, Kidd also served as a prior advisor at Ripple and Square, both payment and financial service providers. Greg Kidd showed his interest in the building of a portable identity and digital currencies in the projects invested. Mask Network is proud to be part of the Hard Yaka portfolio, and we are excited to build the easy-to-use portal to Web 3.0 with help from Hard Yaka.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We love the thought that Mask can help liberate the power of Web 3.0 right on top of those tired Web 2.0 social media rails. Excited!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— — Greg Kidd, co-founder of Hard Yaka&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product from Mask Network is constantly bringing new features to users. In the Mask 2.0 update that took place last year, Mask Network introduced the “MaskID” that aims to help users aggregate their identities on both Web 2.0 and Web 3.0. Mask’s discovery of DID aligns with Kidd’s personal interest, with the help from Hard Yaka, we hope to take user identification among Web 2.0 and Web 3.0 worlds to a whole new level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Everything that exists in Web 2.0 and Web 3.0 that can represent you, will be brought together in one place.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— — Suji Yan, Founder and CEO of Mask Network&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network sincerely appreciates the support from Hard Yaka, not only for their capital and technical backing but also for the support with valuable experience in relevant fields. Mask Network cherishes the recognition from both parties, and with the help from them, we are looking forward to meeting more users in the open, free cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;about-hard-yaka&quot;&gt;About Hard Yaka&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard Yaka is a community of builders, visionaries, and risk takers dedicated to inclusion and access, individual ownership and control, and the reimagining of an internet built on open protocols — from self-sovereign identity to DeFi and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Privacy is NOT DEAD in Web3.0 Socials: Mask Network and Mystiko.Network join forces to make the Web 3.0 social life accessible, affordable and private</title><link href="/2022/03/28/privacy-is-not-dead-in-web3.0-socials-mask-network-and-mystiko.network-join-forces-to-make-the-web-3.0-social-life-accessible-affordable-and-private" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Privacy is NOT DEAD in Web3.0 Socials: Mask Network and Mystiko.Network join forces to make the Web 3.0 social life accessible, affordable and private" /><published>2022-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2022/03/28/privacy-is-not-dead-in-web3.0-socials-mask-network-and-mystiko.network-join-forces-to-make-the-web-3.0-social-life-accessible-affordable-and-private</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2022/03/28/privacy-is-not-dead-in-web3.0-socials-mask-network-and-mystiko.network-join-forces-to-make-the-web-3.0-social-life-accessible-affordable-and-private">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/mystikoxmask.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network and Mystiko.Network will join forces to make privacy affordable and accessible to all Web 3.0 users, bringing freedom and creativity back to creators and the Web 3.0 community. Mystiko.Network will work with Mask Network to provide privacy options to all Web3.0 social partners in the Mask Network ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Life from Web 1.0 to the Web 3.0 Level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are living in a world that requires social interaction with others. The social life of humankind has existed since our very existence and has evolved with technological change. The amount of social interaction between humans has increased exponentially since the creation of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many would categorize the development of the internet into three stages: Web 1.0, Web 2.0, and Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web 1.0 is the earliest form of the internet: users read what is there passively. The contents are limited, and the power to post is restricted. The power to post started to change in the Web 2.0 era, where most websites and social networks we use today, Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Google, etc fall into that category. In the Web 2.0 era - instead of consuming passively, users can show their creations to others. However, the platforms play a huge role in these interactions, the platforms have the power to remove one’s account, or take down content that is considered inappropriate. Little users can resist because once they post their work onto the platform, they no longer own their creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the era of Web 3.0, things have changed. The demand for self-sovereign identity and ownership is surging. The new generations, especially millennials and Gen-Z, are calling for more power to speak up in social networks, a better way to bond with the like-minded, and a more sustainable way to commercialize their network. It is believed that social connections and creativity should not be distributed by Web 2.0 monopolies, but owned by creators and driven by communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key features that distinguish Web 2.0 and Web 3.0, is the owner of information and data. In Web 2.0, social life, relations, and content were well monetized, but the majority of such profit went to the intermediary social platforms. However, in the Web 3.0 era, the relationship between platform, user, creator, and audience, has changed drastically. With what we called “SocialFi,” people’s social relationship has been directly connected with finance. Every word people typed and posted, and every click of “follow” could be turned into profit that directly goes to the creator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web 3.0 pioneers have come up with innovative solutions to build social networks that truly belong to individuals. For example, Axie Infinity piloted a play-to-earn gaming model and has attracted millions of players to play games and earn income. DAOs, such as ConstitutionDAO, also reshaped the way people work with each other. Within DAO, members are brought together not only because they support the same cause, but also because they know their contribution will grant them ownership of the DAO’s benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After taking our fair share of profit in Web3.0 social life, what is next? Privacy, security, and better accessibility.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The paradigm of social networks has shifted, but the freedom of speech and the value of creativity are yet to be maximized until the privacy of on-chain data is realized.&lt;/strong&gt; While speeches are appreciated, creativity is rewarded, and campaign initiators are encouraged to lead their community with vision, the unencrypted data of related messages and transparent financial flow on public chains are still at the stake of being leaked and exploited by unwanted actors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With most crypto users entering the crypto realm via KYC in centralized exchanges, the majority of data flow related to crypto is transparent, and that means any crypto users’ personal life can easily be decoded based on their or their network’s on-chain payment records. Imagine how it is like to have all your digital traces exposed to the public or lost control of your assets simply because you tipped a creator or made an online payment with crypto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a ‘100% transparent person’, anyone could be vulnerable and exposed to potential threats. For example, governance can still track and trace specific social campaign leaders and supporters; and hackers can attack high-profile creators. Centralized exchanges could potentially make on-chain data less transparent, but they can always shut down personal financial accounts for political reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, after reshaping the profit-sharing mechanism, security and privacy of social networks are essential next steps in truly giving power back to creators and communities in Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;mystikonetwork-and-mask-network-join-forces-to-make-the-web-30-social-life-accessible-affordable-and-private&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mystiko.Network and Mask Network join forces to make the Web 3.0 social life accessible, affordable, and private&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy creates a comfort zone for freedom of speech and creativity. The privacy technology behind the equity and freedom of online social networks shall be secure, affordable, and accessible to all.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security:&lt;/strong&gt; Social network data, including messages or financial data, should be hosted and verified on-chain in decentralized manners, keeping data untamperable and securing the data ownership of users.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy:&lt;/strong&gt; Info flow, both messages and financial data, shall be encrypted and controlled only by users&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessibility&lt;/strong&gt;: privacy should be a simple one-click experience for the user, and a ‘plug-and-play’ adoption experience for developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mystiko.Network,&lt;/strong&gt; the universal Web 3.0 financial privacy SDK, &lt;strong&gt;and Mask Network,&lt;/strong&gt; a pioneer in social data privacy, &lt;strong&gt;will join forces to make Web 3.0 social network secure, private, affordable and accessible to all,&lt;/strong&gt; bringing freedom and creativity value back to creators and the community in the era of Web3.0. Mystiko.Network will work with Mask Network and provide privacy options to all Web3.0 social partners in the Mask Network ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mystiko.Network, the universal Web 3.0 financial privacy SDK.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​​Mystiko.Network is the base layer of web3 with both connectivity and confidentiality, leveraging zero-knowledge proof with industry leading “zk of zk” technology. &lt;strong&gt;Mystiko.Network is building the ultimate universal web3 privacy infrastructure through PaaS (Privacy as an SDK)&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing any social networks stakeholders to easily activate transaction privacy easily:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For blockchains. Any L1 and L2 blockchains could utilize Mystiko.Network as a privacy layer, making their mainnet transactions confidential both within the same chain or from/to other chains.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For bridges. Any cross-chain bridges could utilize Mystiko.Network to add privacy bridging functions, making cross-chain transactions fully private. The first privacy bridge application built on Mystiko.Network is already live. &lt;a href=&quot;https://testnet.wallet.mystiko.network/&quot; title=&quot;https://testnet.wallet.mystiko.network/&quot;&gt;https://testnet.wallet.mystiko.network/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For wallets. Any wallet could utilize Mystiko.Network to add private asset management and private transactions features. The first privacy wallet application built on Mystiko.Network is already live with MetaMask.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For Dapps: Any dapps could utilize Mystiko.Network to provide users with on-chain financial privacy features, e.g. private DEX and private on-chain crypto payments dapps that protect receivers/merchants’ income history. Private tipping for SocialFi Dapp to secure the privacy of creators and supporters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mask Network, pioneer in social data privacy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has created an extension that helps users encrypt messages that they want to send on mainstream social networks, so that the messages cannot be censored by the platform. Mask Network also made traditional social platforms unable to obtain user data while avoiding being banned by these platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;**No centralized services.&lt;br /&gt;
**The encrypted posts are stored directly on those social network platforms and the encrypted keys are synced in GunDB (&lt;a href=&quot;http://gun.eco/&quot; title=&quot;http://gun.eco/&quot;&gt;http://gun.eco/&lt;/a&gt;), which ensures Mask Network would not be impacted by any malfunction or other deliberate attack on servers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;**No dependencies on centralized APIs from those platforms.&lt;br /&gt;
**All the actions on Mask Network, e.g. creating new posts, uploading photos, getting post content and decrypting, etc., are realized by simulating one’s real operation. In principle, as long as a real person can still use Facebook or Twitter normally on their computer, Mask Network’s extension will work just fine.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No information leakage while Mask works.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mask Network interface is being attached as a ShadowDOM, which websites cannot choose to disable, and would never know the Mask extension is being attached on their website. All the content posted on these platforms, including keyboard typing, can no longer be monitored and stored by major platforms anymore. &lt;strong&gt;This would ultimately protect the user’s privacy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The synergy of Mystiko.Network and Mask Network will unlock the potential of Web 3.0 social life, and we cannot wait to see what is next.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mystiko.Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mystiko.Network is the base layer of web3 with both connectivity and confidentiality. Leveraging zero-knowledge proof with industry leading “zk of zk” technology, Mystiko.Network guarantees &lt;strong&gt;interoperability, scalability and privacy&lt;/strong&gt;, all at once. Mystiko.Network is building the ultimate universal web3 privacy infrastructure through PaaS (Privacy as an SDK).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mystiko.network&quot;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://testnet.wallet.mystiko.network/&quot;&gt;Testnet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MystikoNetwork&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/Mystiko_Network&quot;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://discord.gg/mystikonetwork&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Mystiko.Network&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;｜&lt;a href=&quot;https://mystiko.network/whitepaper.pdf&quot;&gt;Whitepaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.mystiko.network/&quot;&gt; Doc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry></feed>